Hello everyone! I'm Misato Otani from Equal Love!
I'm Cara Saito, and this is Morisa.
I'm Morisa, and I came to the studio where this kitchen is located today because I heard that we're going to shoot a YouTube video.
I'm not sure if it's going to be okay.
The fact that these three were brought together... makes me feel like I'm being brought together as if I can't cook at all.
It's frustrating.
We'll do our best. We don't know who's going to cook.
But we're cooking today.
I think it's gonna be a little bit of a letdown. I can see a little bit more.
I can see a little bit more.
Have you made anything lately?
Scrumptious.
That's great. It burns like hotcakes.
Did you get it on the couch?
No, but it was delicious.
It was good. I'm glad.
Where's Risa?
The other day, I almost blew up. I was too scared to use the microwave.
It smelled really burnt.
What? How is it?
Huh? Well?
Huh? How's it going?
I asked you a question.
I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
I make a lot of food. Like peperoncino.
Wow, you even mentioned the name of the dish.
It's a totally different level.
I might be able to make it if I look at the recipe.
Oh, something came. A directive.
It's in an envelope.
Scary.
What is it?
I'll read it.
Order form.
Hello, Ricoh lovers!
Today, we have a promotional video for Mr. Misugan's Cantance!
Oh!
In order to show you the appeal of Cantance, I'm going to give you a recipe for a dish that you're going to be cooking.
Please watch it and make today's lunch for everyone! From the staff
Oh? I see.
Cantance?
Cantance means that it's so easy that even a bad cook can do it.
I think so.
Can we do it?
It's a cantance.
It says we can do it.
I think we can make it.
I think I can make it.
I'm looking at the recipe.
It's good, isn't it?
If you make it in Japan...
You can make it.
It's fine. It's fine.
It's like making one for each of us.
I see.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors to decide the order.
Let's play rock, paper, scissors.
First, let's play rock-paper-scissors-paper.
Ah...
First.
Okay, you two.
First, rock, paper, scissors.
Number two.
I'll go third.
I don't think that's a problem.
I'll do my best.
It won't matter
Yes, sir.
Do your best.
I'll do my best.
Do your best
Good luck.
agency
Oh!
I'm going to start cooking now.
I actually have a cantaloupe. I use it for dumpling sauce.
I've never used it for cooking.
What do you mean? Teriyaki chicken.
It's all in Roman letters.
Is that what this is about?
I'm just... what?
I'll do my best to decipher it.
What are we making?
Teri-mati chicken. Why don't we just make teri-mati chicken?
Arranger Chicken Timing in Four Flying Pans with Skinsides...
What's skin-side?
Wait, I really don't know.
Well, I don't really know, but I'm pretty sure it's the only seasoning we have, because we only have vinegar.
Oil... well, let's put oil on it first.
Grease it up.
Get a flying pan.
Frying pan.
Once you cook the meat.
I think I'm gonna fry it.
What kind of meat is this?
Is this chicken?
I'll put this in there too.
Oh, it looks like chicken.
I think it's chicken.
Oh, no!
It's bouncing!
I'm frying it.
I thought you were supposed to add cold carbs.
Soy milk! Cold soymilk!
Wow! It smells so good!
What's that, like, a song? Is it written? You mean...
Sing?
It's so easy, it's so easy.
Oh, my God, I'm so embarrassed.
But I can do it.
Let's put some vegetables in it.
Mushrooms sound good.
I'll add tomatoes.
Smells good.
It's so colorful.
It's so rich!
Vegetables too!
There's something like beets.
It's pretty and colorful, so let's put it in.
I'll fry it with this.
It looks so good.
Looks amazing.
Looks delicious!
Kantansu has all kinds of seasonings in it.
It's going to make it delicious.
Look at the char on this one.
It looks so good.
It looks so good, but isn't this how it's supposed to be served? If you fry it a little more...
I think it's going to be good.
I'm going to serve it.
Favourite side dish.
Maybe we shouldn't fry them together.
Serving is the most important part of cooking, right?
What a pretty shade!
Finally, what's this?
This...
Put it on top.
And it's done!
Teriyuma Chicken!
It looks so delicious!
I think this is it. I think I did everything as instructed.
I was surprised at how good it smells with just one seasoning!
I'm going to start cooking now!
I'm looking forward to seeing some vegetables from plants I've never seen before. I've heard that you're taking on a new challenge today.
Recipe: Yes, thank you very much!
Wait a minute! What do you mean it's all in English?
Teriyaki, umami, chekin.
Oh, what? Oh, no. Wait a minute.
Arang, arang, arang.
Chicken titty gig, meat in a flying pan, beads in a flying pan, chicken side down.
How did you do that?
Side down. Down to the right? Right?
You put the meat next to the bread and then you put the chicken on top of it and then you fry it?
What about the bread? That doesn't translate to bread. It's Roman. Pen? Pen? Pen? I don't know.
And rolling. All of it. Untill. Did you learn this? "Untill." "Untill." "Untill.
I learned it, but I don't remember what it is.
Chicken. Oh, chicken. This? Oil... Oil?
it says "rolling" so you roll it, then you drizzle it, then you shake it a little.
I don't know...
2-2, follow the easy numbers, rhythm, easy numbers...
Oh!
Chickens.
No. Seckins? Seckins? Not "Chickens." Seckins?
Seckins? What?
Grottencolor.
Oh, yeah, green, red... a variety of colors.
I think if we do a few simple numbers, we'll be fine.
Alson, Favaretto. Favaretto.
Favaretto side dish. Oh, you like tuna? Tuna?
I thought you could read better.
So from the frying pan. There it is again.
Frying pan over it
Chai for Max.
Hmmm...
Over on Sunday Over it
Overflying? I knew it.
Maybe he knows what he's doing. I'm not sure.
In the meantime, we're going to use a few simple numbers to make a Terry-uma Chicken.
What?
I'm going to make Terry's Chicken using simple numbers.
I don't understand at all! What should I do? I'll just roll it in oil.
I'll just roll it in oil for now.
They say chicken takes a long time to cook.
I think it's too much.
I think I'll put the chicken on the stove and then light it.
I'm scared.
I managed to get it lit.
Oh, it's burning... it's burning...
It's burning.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
I'm so embarrassed.
I don't even want to play a role.
I'm so greasy.
We should put some water in it.
Water?
No water?
I feel Brazilian
YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAATH
Meat for now
Meat.
Now that the chicken is done
Side down
Rolling
Kucket Inside
I don't know
Withskin side
Maybe that's a side and you want me to put a vegetable in it.
Maybe I'll put this in.
Okay, I'll put this in.
I don't know.
I don't know if vegetables are supposed to be cooked.
Wait.
Maybe I'll put this chicken in too.
I don't know.
I'll add some tomatoes to make it more colorful.
I'd like to go to number 2.
Poi in cansans.
I'm going to put in the cantaloupe.
So, cansans, right?
Let's put it in.
Let's see, let's take the top end down.
Cançance.
Put it in.
Too much? One more time.
There you go.
I'm so happy.
I've been wanting to try this ever since I saw the commercial.
I'm just going to stir-fry it.
I don't know, so I'll move on to the next one.
I'm not sure, so I'll move on to the next one.
Save
Save with your fayeberette side
So Faye Barrettside is going to be a mushroom.
Me, yesterday.
I dreamt that I cut my finger
I had a dream that I cut off my finger with a knife.
Eh, it might be a little scary
Yikes!
Did I just get it right at this moment?
It doesn't fit.
Okay, Bromza.
Oh, okay, a little bit stronger.
A little stronger at the end.
I'd like to finish strong.
Oh, my God!
I'm so happy with that sound.
Hmmm...
Well then, I'd like to start serving!
First of all, let's look at this
It looks like a sinagina!
But we're going to use an appetizer.
First of all, let's put the mushrooms on top of the teriyaki, so we'll put the chicken on top.
We'll put the chicken on top.
My mom is going to be so mad at me.
It's done!
I've never really made this before.
I've only made a few before.
It was so easy to make!
It's a "kantansan no okune"!
I hope you will try making it, too!
I would like to start cooking!
Recipe of cooking
Yes, please!
Wait!
Wait, it's not Japanese!
Teri-rima Chicken
Ah yes!
Chicken Meat Fried Bread Skin Sight Down
Cook over medium.
You mean medium heat?
Rolling, rolling.
(2) put the cantaloupe in.
(3) is is-your-favorite-sight-dish.
I guess that means you can serve it with whatever you like.
What is it?
Just this and a story
Two people a little while ago.
I think you got the meat wrong.
What? Really?
What are we doing here?
What is chicken, by the way?
Well, when I think of teniyaki...
It's kind of an art form.
I think it's something like this.
I'm thinking...
I'm going to use this.
For now, I'm going to bake it.
I'll bake it.
Wait, I'm scared...
It says "medium heat".
It says "medium heat.
it's medium heat, so it looks like medium heat
put oil in the pan.
Maybe not too much.
Like this?
Spread it out a little bit like this.
So it doesn't stick.
And then...
Put this in.
And put the meat in.
Here we go.
Wait a minute. I'm scared. Here we go.
About three pieces.
Wait, I'm scared. I'm scared!
I'm always afraid of bouncing.
Whenever I do this, I always need someone to help me.
I'm scared!
Wait, doesn't it look good?
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, but I'm scared. I can't stop.
I've always had this mysterious confidence.
Maybe it's all in the seasoning.
But...
I'd like to put it in.
It's the seasoning that counts.
Oh, that's good.
I'm sure it's going to be good.
It's going to be good.
I'm scared! Won't it stop?
This much, I think.
I hope it tastes good.
It smells so good, too.
That means it's got flavor.
Oh, man.
It's so easy!
Well, I think I've had enough of this.
I'd like to put it on a plate.
Turn off the heat.
I'm going to put it on a plate.
Do it right.
Nice and clean.
We're going to add a little bit of color to make it a little bit more visual.
Add the tomatoes.
Can we eat them raw like this?
What? Is it big?
Oh! I should've laid it out!
Let's try it again.
Let's do it again. Maybe like this.
Wait a minute.
Okay, this is the sauce.
It's got a nice flavor to it, so I'm just going to put a little bit on it.
It's so good!
It's great!
Delumah chicken is ready!
I just grilled the meat and boiled it briefly.
I think I did it very well!
Yay!
So, everyone's food is ready!
It's so rich!
I can't believe I made it, too!
There's some kind of amazing yeast.
Sure, I can hear it.
It's from an Italian restaurant.
With a coating of mushrooms, too.
This one's actually the same width as Risachi's.
I baked it, and it became supple
I baked them. They look delicious, but
I'm sure it tastes great
Well, let's have it, shall we?
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Yum! Yum!
It's so, so, so good!
Super delicious! It's amazing!
Because he loves having the seasoning.
Just this one. Amazing.
Mr. Otani, Mr. Cucumber, can you taste the chicken?
Mokkero!
I put two kinds of meat in it.
This one?
This? What?
Pork?
Did we do it?
You got it?
Let's write down the recipe.
Cantons.
Cantons?
Pour in the rhythm of "Cantance".
I did this.
Cantance.
I've seen it on the commercials.
I could do it!
I did it! I'm two episodes in.
I'm clear!
I had no idea what this was.
It's English for "cook the meat until it shines.
Golden color.
That's right.
It's called golden brown.
That's why it's called "golden brown".
I see.
And then there's the bread.
Prime bread.
That's quite all right.
You've learned quite a bit.
I learned a lot.
Mmm!
Delicious.
You put it in just right.
It's more important than you think.
What's more...
I didn't know one could be so good.
I'm sure we can make it together.
We can make it.
All we did was grill the meat and pour it on top.
It's like we're three guys who can cook.
I think we can do it.
I'm sure you'll be great.
There's so many flavors.
It's true.
It's good for you.
Purity of pace?
Purity.
Pure Pace?
There's also "pure pace" and "pure pace".
I thought I'd start cooking with it.
That's good.
It's easy to use. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
As soon as I think of it, it's easy to do, it only takes a few minutes.
I hope you all enjoy today's mango high.
I hope you'll try to make it!
Please try to make it!
Easy number
Bye bye!